{
    "id": "13026ed4b2fc4cb5a361e13df0f6d162",
    "title": "Few or little",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "c33e87206c32490f8bc16bfe582bdc04",
            "title": "Few Or Little",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I have a ……………. friends in Malaysia.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "little",
                        "less"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has ..................... interest in politics.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "little",
                        "few",
                        "a few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He won’t make a good teacher. He has very ………………… patience.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "little",
                        "less"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "There is only a ………………. oil left.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "less",
                        "few",
                        "little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have visited Japan a …………… times.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "little",
                        "less"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I watched a ………………. films on the weekend.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "little",
                        "less"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is a busy executive. He has got very …………. spare time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "little",
                        "less"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t think I will pass the test. I could answer only a ………………. questions.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "little",
                        "less"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "His latest book was not a success. Only a ……………… copies were sold.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "little",
                        "less"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I only like a ………………. sugar in my tea.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "little",
                        "few",
                        "less"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}